https://www.phenomenews.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested
this privacy declaration we would like to confirm out commitment to keeping the personal information of all visitors and users of this Web site private. We, at https://www.phenomenews.com place great importance on the privacy of everyone that interacts with us. Below you will find complete information on our policies regarding personal data collection and distribution.
We know the value of keeping your personal information private. It is our policy to keep the website’s visitors and users informed about the methods which we use for personal data collection, processing and keeping. We safeguard your data when you provide it to us while trying to assist you in making well-informed decisions. Our goal is to update our policy in line with changes and advancements in technologies, business and customer relations.
What Kind of Data Do We Gather?
There are two types of information collected by us from visitors to our website https://www.phenomenews.com – personal information disclosed willingly by you and web site use data gathered on a cumulative basis from all visitors as they browse the Web site.
1. Personal Information that You Choose to Disclose
Registration Information
This information is provided by you personally, when you register for any of the products and services on this website. This includes registration for newsletters.
Email Information
In case you decide to communicate with us via email, we may keep your email address and the entire content of the correspondence between you and us. We use the same privacy protection measures to safeguard your personal data and the messages that you send to us that we employ when information is provided via telephone and mail.
2. Web Site Use Information
This Web site has standard technology typical for commercial Web sites called “cookies” (please find an explanation of what cookies are below) and web server log files. These tools are used for collecting information on the use of this Web site. The information collected through these tools may include times and dates of visits, time spent on this Web site, the Web pages visited, the Web sites visited before and after your visit to our Web site.
What Do We Do with the Information You Leave with Us?
We use the information that you provide to us for various purposes. It is used for product and service delivery, for payment processing and for monitoring the use of services. We use the data provided by visitors for the purpose of marketing and promoting our products and services. Web site content improvement and customization of content, layout and services are among the other legally permitted purposes which we use personal data for. These are all methods that allow us to make our Web site better for you to use.
The sharing of this kind of information on a cumulative basis is possible. Personal information and business information will not be disclosed to third parties except for the cases in which this is required by law.
Seldom, we may use the information gathered by us to send you notifications of changes to our Web site, newly introduced services, exclusive offers and of other events which may be of interest to you. You have the right to notify us that you do not wish to receive such notifications at any time. You can do this by writing an email to us at the link available on our newsletter.
Cookies – What Are They?
A cookie is a tiny text document. Usually, it has an anonymous identifying code that is unique. Upon visiting a Web site, its server will ask your computer whether cookies can be stored on your hard drive in a special section designated for these text documents. Technically, if your website permits it, any Web site can send cookies to your computer. However, for the purpose of privacy protection, the browser allows each and every Web site to access only its own cookies on your computer. It cannot access the text documents sent by other Web sites. Most browsers are technically set to receive cookies. Still, you may set your browser not to accept them. If you choose this option, some of the parts of our Web site may not function properly when you visit it. It is not possible for a cookie to collect any other information from your hard drive or to infect your machine with a computer virus.
What Do We Do with Data We Gather from Cookies?
Our Web site employs cookies to set you apart from others when you visit it. Often, cookies are used to prevent you from logging in more than required for security purposes. Together with our Web server’s log files, cookies are utilized to compute the cumulative number of unique visitors to our website. They are also used to determine which of its pages are most visited. In this way, we collect technical data feedback which we use for improving our website so that it serves our clients better. Cookies do not enable us to gather personal data. We do not deliberately keep any personal information made available to us by your browser in your cookies.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, PhenomeNEWS has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
IP Addresses
When you are connected to the internet, your computer uses IP addresses. Your IP address is a code that is used by servers on the network to identify your computer. Our Web server gathers IP addresses automatically. These are part of traffic data (demographic and profile information). They are used in order for Web site data, for instance pages that you request, to be made available to you.
Information Sharing and Sale
Information that may be used to identify a visitor (for instance email address and personal data) is not shared, sold, lent or leased by us to anyone expect to the level required to process payments or deliver services that you have asked for.
How Can You Access and Change Your Information?
Please, feel free to email us at the provided address with a request to access your personal data that we have collected and keep in our database.
How About Legally Required Provision of Data?
We may disclose information in case we are legally obliged to do it. Basically, we may do this if we, in good faith, believe that it is required by law or to protect our legal rights. We may reveal user account information if we consider that the disclosure of this data is necessary to identify, get in touch with or bring legal action against an individual who may have breached our Terms of Service or to preserve the security of our Web site’s users and the general public.
How About Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?
We do not bear any responsibility for the practices, information and content of Web sites that have inbound links or outbound links to or from our Web site. In many cases, links to other sites are provided solely for information purposes in order to benefit users.
Please, take into account the fact that when you follow a link from our Web site to visit another one, our Privacy Policy is no longer applicable. When you browse and use another Web site, which may or may not have a link on our Web site, this is subject to the other Web site’s regulations, terms and conditions. Please, go over those before continuing your browsing.
Your Consent
When you are using our Web site, you permit us to collect, keep and use your personal data as thoroughly explained in this Privacy Policy. We keep the right to make changes to this policy when we deem fit with or without notification.
Our Data Security Obligation:
Please keep in mind that your data will be kept and used on our computers in the USA. The US laws on personal data keeping may be less strict than the ones in your country. For the purposes of unauthorized access prevention, data accuracy maintenance and correct use of data, we have adopted adequate physical, managerial and electronic procedures. These are used to protect the data which we gather online.
Choice/Subscription/Unsubscribing
Our policy gives you the option to unsubscribe for receiving messages from us. Upon unsubscribing, we will stop sending messages to you immediately when this is technically possible.
Surveys & Contests
Occasionally, we request data from visitors through surveys and contests. Participation in these is voluntary. You can choose whether to disclose information or not. The requested information may include personal details (name and address) and demographic data (zip code, age). Contact information is used for notifying winning participants. Survey data is used for improving the services provided on this Web site.
About Children
Minors should not use our Web site. We request that visitors to our Web site under the age of 18 do not provide any personal data to us. All persons under the age of 18 are denied access to https://www.phenomenews.com
Ownership Changes and Acquisition
In case this Web site or a significant portion of its assets are purchased, your data will be regarded as part of these assets. It may be part of these transferred assets.
Policy Changes
We keep the right to make amendments to this policy. When this is done, we will notify users who have permitted us to do so via email. Changes will be posted on this page as well. Please, rest assured that irrespective of future Privacy Policy amendments, we will not use personal data provided to us under this Privacy Policy in any way that is not in agreement with it without your permission.
2014-10-16
David
Recommended
Recent Posts
My CRAZY Edge Bioactives Spartagen XT Review – Deadly Side Effects?
A Fish Will Help Me Get Girls? – The Tao of Badass Review – Pre-selection?
Can You Create Uncontrollable LUST? The Desire System Review – By Dr. David Tian
3 Questions to Seduction? – My CRAZY Vin Dicarlo Pandora’s Box System Review
Does Literotica Work? The Girlfriend Activation System Review GFAS – Don’t Buy It?
Copyright © 2016 PhenomeNEWS | Terms and Disclaimer | Privacy Policy | DMCA Notice | Contact
